{"cards":[{"mId":"7c813752-7c7f-45fe-994a-dea25be1ac1d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Legislation","mBack":"A law or set of laws suggested by a government and made official by a parliament."},{"mId":"ac44a312-efdc-491e-a409-0b868d6a13e7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Deter","mBack":"To make someone less enthusiastic about doing something by threatening bad results if they do it."},{"mId":"aa77ded1-3c17-4e4d-8d0a-facba3e0e0e9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Offender","mBack":"Someone who is guilty of a crime."},{"mId":"635c59fc-d051-4055-b72e-2530f5473ba3","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Punish","mBack":"To cause someone who has done something wrong or committed a crime to suffer, by hurting them, forcing them to pay money, sending them to prison, etc"},{"mId":"510b608e-d1b6-4ba5-9612-4d3f7c1fd664","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Prevention","mBack":"When you stop something from happening or stop someone from doing something."},{"mId":"10944c63-671a-494b-87f3-e5d37bb1d2fb","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Commit","mBack":"To do something illegal or something that is considered wrong."},{"mId":"541569d9-eb8a-46cc-bf36-23a366f4e077","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Criminal","mBack":"A person who commits a crime."},{"mId":"92d936da-3110-4b4a-87e9-9f76d39f1435","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Probation","mBack":"A period of time when a criminal must behave well and not commit any more crimes in order to avoid being sent to prison"},{"mId":"2542cdeb-05b7-4c7a-822e-31fca94d34ec","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Rehabilitate","mBack":"To return someone or something to a good or healthy condition, state or way of living."},{"mId":"ece6d836-06db-499a-983d-bb3d434fbfb6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Guilt","mBack":"Having done something wrong or committed a crime."},{"mId":"bec71cda-f880-4807-ad98-994887673444","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Jury","mBack":"A group of people chosen to decide in a court of law if someone is guilty of a crime or not."},{"mId":"23a9164b-eec9-4305-a6fb-fa0253cf4250","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Convict","mBack":"To decide officially in a court of law that someone is guilty of a crime."},{"mId":"ce2bb7d7-18db-403a-b60e-54df5bebe92c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Fine","mBack":"Being made to pay money for breaking the law."},{"mId":"5ea19b9a-ebb8-4798-be3c-c229ad9b4a4c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Imprisonment","mBack":"Being put in prison."},{"mId":"5442ab7a-9f45-452c-8e32-33a6cc3309bc","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Community Service","mBack":"Work that people do to help other people without payment, and which young criminals whose crime was not serious enough for them to be put in prison are sometimes ordered to do."},{"mId":"cf8a7262-b52d-4a3d-813e-371be9c79f17","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Justice","mBack":"Fairness in the way people are dealt with."},{"mId":"00f57ce2-528e-4efb-bf0d-3d2a784f3dac","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Victim","mBack":"Someone who has suffered because of the actions of someone else."}]}